# MINHVAN LE

Mple330@gmail.com | 206.747.7003 http://www.linkedin.com/in/minhvanle06

#### PROJECT MANAGEMENT | ACCOUNT MANAGEMENT

Ambitious and driven young professional with experience in project and account management. Key strengths include leadership, communication, attention to detail and follow through. Ability to partner with management to develop strategies to improve efficiency and quickness in projects with minimum or no errors. Strategic and self-motivated thinker able to manage several tasks and perform under pressure in fast-paced, deadline-focused environments.

Skills and Core Competencies						
<ul> <li>Project Management</li> </ul>	<ul> <li>Relationship Building</li> </ul>	<ul> <li>Microsoft Word, Excel,</li> </ul>				
<ul> <li>Account Management</li> </ul>	<ul><li>Process Analysis</li></ul>	PowerPoint, Outlook,				
<ul> <li>Strategy Development</li> </ul>	<ul> <li>Social Networking</li> </ul>	Access & Publisher				
<ul> <li>Training/Development</li> </ul>	<ul> <li>Teamwork/Team Building</li> </ul>	<ul> <li>Data Entry</li> </ul>				
Professional Experiences						

# Systems Source | Seattle, WA| Sept. 2018 - June 2020

# Managed all types of requests from multiple sources through effective prioritization and time management ranging from simple to complex requests.

**Account Coordinator** 

- Key strategist in creation and spearheaded different programs such as Stocking program and Online Portal Program that was used and implemented across multiple clients company wide.
- Coordinated and handled confidential information pertaining to personal performance matters, labor relation, negotiations, and other communication.
- Independently arranged and coordinated meetings, installations, deliveries, pickups and dropoffs.
- Prepared and delegated reports for external and internal clients for weekly, monthly, and quarterly reports.
- Managed high profile clients such as Seattle Children's Hospital, City of Seattle, and University of Washington.

## Nordstrom | Seattle, WA | Sept. 2017- Sept. 2018 Merchandise Coordinator

- Worked directly with Buying Teams on various projects to ensure products get to all stores quickly and efficiently to maximize profit.
- Demonstrated ability to simultaneously work on 10+ projects at a given time on a daily basis completed within a specified SLA.
- Built and maintained strong relations with internal and external business partners by raising metrics from 60-70% to 95-100% each month.
- Served as the first point of contact for all vendor service requests and escalations. Handled inbound service requests
  and ensure that they are properly addressed in a timely manner.

NA MINHVAN LE Résumé – Page 2

- Liaise with other internal departments as required to resolve vendor's issues and questions.
- Utilized problem-solving, analytic, and multi-tasking skills to ensure each assignment meet deadline.
- Delivered timely, accurate and professional operational support to all vendors within a specified SLA.
- Demonstrated excellent time-management skills and the ability to work independently while utilizing resources, policies and procedures.

# Nordstrom | Seattle, WA | Dec. 2016- Sept. 2017 Merchandise Specialist

- Managed creation of new suppliers, vendors, brands, and labels from beginning to end.
- Helped vendors onboard new and existing self-support services.
- Served as the first point of contact for all vendor service requests and escalations. Handle inbound service requests
  and ensure that they are properly addressed.
- Utilized problem-solving, analytic, and multi-tasking skills to ensure each assignment meet deadline.
- Delivered timely, accurate and professional operational support to all vendors within a specified SLA.
- Analyzed business processes for optimization, create proposals to business partners and implement a new process for time reduction.
- Managed integration process of multiple Nordstrom systems, such as Nordstrom Rack, Hautelook, and JWN Systems
  of over 1.5K business partners for seamless transition.

## U.S. Bank | Seattle, WA | 2013 – 2016 Teller Coordinator

- Supported manager in their absence, scheduling staff based on key strengths to streamline operations.
- Managed and led a small team, supplying them with tools and resources to consistently maintain excellence in operations and compliance.
- Worked 20+ hours a week while being a full time student.
- Provided exceptional customer service backed by Gallup, Inc.
- Exceeded sales goal quarterly by 200% minimally each quarter.
- Exceeded personal quotas to ensure branch reached their weekly targets.
- Suggested financial solutions for clients to help meet their financial goals.
- Provided outstanding customer service while assisting customers with requests including accepting/processing deposits and loan payments.
- Recognition for Outstanding Performance Fall Quarter 2015 Top Referral/Credit Card Sales
- Recognition for Highest Customer Satisfaction Ratings Spring 2015

NA MINHVAN LE Résumé – Page 3

#### **EDUCATION**

# University of Washington | Seattle, WA | 2016 Bachelor of Arts in Communication

 Relevant Coursework: Social Science Communication Research, Interpersonal Communication, Business & Economic Calculus, Accounting, Statistical Methods

# **V**OLUNTEERISM

# Food Lifeline | Seattle, WA | 2021

• Volunteer: Sorting and packing a variety of food for distribution to other food banks - 30+ hours

#### **CERTIFICATION**

## University of Washington | Seattle, WA | Sept. - Dec. 2021

• Full Stack Web Development - In Progress

PROFICIENCIES					
•	HTML5	•	React	•	Express
•	CSS	•	NodeJS	•	Bootstrap
•	Javascript	•	MySql	•	MongoDB
	JQuery		Sequelize		Git/GitHub